Guide to the Carol D. Litchfield microbiology collection, 1924-1997
George Mason University Libraries
- Carol D. Litchfield Microbiology collection, 1924-1997
  - Experimental Approaches to Limnology, 1973 (Box 3, Volume 5)
    Reprinted from Journal of the Fisheries Research Board of Canada Vol. 30, No. 10, p. 1409-1552
    2 Copies
  - Journal of the Fisheries Research Board of Canada, February 1971 (Box 3, Volume 6)
    Editor: J.C. Stevenson
    Volume 28, No. 2
  - Notes on Fishes from the Firth of Clyde, 1926 (Box 3, Volume 7)
    Richard Elmhirst
    Booklet, Reprinted from "The Scottish Naturalist," September-October 1926
  - Methods for the Estimation of Production of Aquatic Animals, 1971 (Box 3, Volume 8)
    Edited by: G.G. Winberg, Translated from Russian by: Annie Duncan
    Handbook for production estimates for both marine and freshwater invertebrates
  - Antillean Fish Guide, 1973 (Box 3, Volume 9)
    Bart de Boer, Dick Hoogerwerf, Ingvar Kristensen, Jankees Post
    Identification guide
  - Estuarine Coastal and Shelf Science, 1982 (Box 3, Volume 10)
    Published by: Academic Press Inc. (London)
    Contents and index of Volume 14 of Estuarine Coastal and Shelf Science
  - Estuarine Coastal and Shelf Science, January 1982 (Box 3, Volume 11)
    Volume 14 Number 1
  - Estuarine Coastal and Shelf Science, March 1982 (Box 3, Volume 12)
    Volume 14 Number 3
  - Estuarine Coastal and Shelf Science, April 1982 (Box 3, Volume 13)
    Volume 14 Number 4
  - Estuarine Coastal and Shelf Science, May 1982 (Box 3, Volume 14)
    Volume 14 Number 5
  - Estuarine Coastal and Shelf Science, June 1982 (Box 3, Volume 15)
    Volume 14 Number 6
  - Third Forum on Innovative Hazardous Waste Treatment Technologies: Domestic and International, June 1991 (Box 3, Volume 16)
    EPA
    Government report - abstract proceedings, EPA/540/2-92/016
  - Technology Screening Guide for Treatment of CERCLA Soils and Sludges, September 1988 (Box 3, Volume 17)
    Government Report, EPA/540/2-88/004
  - Solid Waste Management Selected Topics, 1985 (Box 3, Volume 18)
    WHO - Copenhagen, Edited by: Michael J. Suess
    Disposal on Land, Composting, Incineration, Animal Waste
  - An Estimate of Benthic Macrofaunal Production in the Offshore Mud of the Northumberland Coast, 1974 (Box 3, Volume 19)
    J.B. Buchanan, R.M. Warwick
    Booklet, stamped with "Contributions from the Dove Marine Laboratory"
  - Sewage Sludge Disposal, 1978 (Box 3, Volume 20)
    Editor: Mona F. Smith
    Volume 2. 1975 - May 1978, NTIS/PS-78/0576
  - Sludge Treatment and Disposal, Sludge Disposal, 1978 (Box 3, Volume 21)
    Volume 1, EPA-625/4-78-012
  - Sludge Treatment and Disposal, Sludge Disposal, 1978 (Box 3, Volume 22)
    Volume 2, EPA-625/4-78-012
  - Research and Development in Hazardous Waste Management (A Survey of U.S. Centers and Institutes), 1989 (Box 3, Volume 23)
    Prepared by: New York State Center for Hazardous Waste Management
    Survey of U.S. Centers and Institutes
  - Sediment Toxicity Identification Evaluation: Phase I (Characterization), Phase II (Identification) and Phase III (Confirmation) Modifications of Effluent Procedures, September 1991 (Box 3, Volume 24)
    Gerald T. Ankley, Mary K. Schubauer-Berigan, Joseph R. Dierkes, Marta T. Lukasewyez
    Draft, EPA/600/6-91/007
  - Characterization and Laboratory Soil Treatability Studies for Creosote and Pentacholophenol Sludges and Contaminated Soil, September 1988 (Box 3, Volume 25)
    G.D. McGinnis, H. Borazjani, L.K. McFarland, D.F. Pope, D.A. Strobel
    EPA/600/2-88/055, Folder
  - Trace Element Sorption by Sediments and Soils-Sites and Processes, 1977 (Box 3, Volume 26)
    Everett A. Jenne
    Chapter 5, Reprinted from: Symposium on Molybdeum in the Environment, Vol.2, 1977, Chappell, W. and Peterson, K., eds. M. Dekker, Inc., N.Y.
  - Regulatory Impact (Box 3, Volume 27)
    Presentation
  - Understanding Site Remediation, 1990 (Box 3, Volume 28)
    Patrick Eagan
    Program binder
  - Site Assessment on the Petroleum Impacted Soils at the Bond Plywood Facility, October 1993 (Box 4, Volume 1)
    Chester Environmental
    Volume 1 Report of Results
  - Assessing and Treating Contaminated Sediment, November 1991 (Box 4, Volume 2)
    Patrick Eagan, Program Director
    University of Wisconsin Session 1
  - Assessing and Treating Contaminated Sediment, November 1991 (Box 4, Volume 3)
    University of Wisconsin Session 2
  - Sanitary Landfill Design, July 1990 (Box 4, Volume 4)
    Joe Spear, Robert K. Ham, Bert Fowler, Edward Rothschild, Peter Kmet, Dave Daniel, Gene Mitchell
    The College of Engineering University of Wisconsin-Madison, also contains a participation certificate for Carol D. Litchfield
  - The Nation's Hazardous Waste Management Program at a Crossroads, RCRA Implementation Study, July 1990 (Box 4, Volume 5)
    Government report, EPA/530-SW-90-069
  - Approaches for the Remediation of Federal Facility Sites Contaminated with Explosive of Radioactive Wastes, September 1993 (Box 4, Volume 6)
    Handbook, EPA/625/R-93/013
  - Selecting Remediation Techniques for Contaminated Sediment, June 1993 (Box 4, Volume 7)
    Government report, EPA-823-B93-001
  - Occurrence and Fate of Organic Solvent Residues in Anoxic Groundwater at the Gloucester Landfill, Canada, February 1989 (Box 4, Volume 8)
    S. Lesage, R.F. Jackson, M.W. Priddle, P. Riemann
    Manuscript for Environmental Science and Technology, it is to provide information prior to publication
  - Methods of Analysis for Determining the Effects of Herbicides on Soil Micro-organisms and Their Activities, January 1978 (Box 4, Volume 9)
    M.P. Greaves, S.L. Cooper, H.A. Davies, J.A.P. Marsh, G.I. Wingfield
    Weed Research Organization Technical Report No. 45
  - Viral and Bacterial Levels Resulting from the Land Application of Digested Sludge, March 1979 (Box 4, Volume 10)
    Government report, EPA-600/1-79-015
  - Assessment of Disease Rates Among Sewer Workers in Copenhagen, Denmark, January 1978 (Box 4, Volume 11)
    Government report, EPA-600/1-78-007
  - Evaluation of the Possible Impact of Pesticide Legislation on Research and Development Activities of Pesticide Manufacturers, February 1975 (Box 4, Volume 12)
    Arthur D. Little Inc.; Alfred E. Wechsler, Joan E. Harrison, John Neumeyer (Consultant)
    Final Report Volume 1
  - The Linnaeus' Garden and Museum at Uppsala, Undated (Box 5, Volume 1)
    Arvid Hjalmar Uggla, revised by: Carl-Otto Von Sydow and Rudolf Zietler
    Pamphlet
  - Linnaeus' Hammarby, 1971 (Box 5, Volume 2)
    Rutger Sernander
    Pamphlet and three postcards of Linnaeus
  - Guidance on EPA Oversight of Remedial Designs and Remedial Actions Performed by Potentially Responsible Parties, April 1990 (Box 5, Volume 3)
    Interim Final, EPA/540/G-90/001
  - Standard Operating Safety Guides, July 1988 (Box 5, Volume 4)
  - Guidance to Environmental Site Assessments, September 1992 (Box 5, Volume 5)
    The Association of Ground Water Scientists and Engineers, A Division of National Ground Water Association
    Manual for A Performance of an ESA
  - Third EPA/Industry Meeting Partnerships in Bioremediation, October 1993 (Box 5, Volume 6)
    Government report, EPA/600/R-93/196
  - Superfund Innovative Technology Evaluation Program Technology Profiles Sixth Edition, November 1993 (Box 5, Volume 7)
    Government report, EPA/540/R-93/526
  - Wisconsin Biotechnology Companies and related firms, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Volume 8)
    University of Wisconsin Biotechnology Center
    Directory
  - Proceedings of the Second Annual Hazardous Materials Management Conference/Central, 1989 (Box 5, Volume 9)
    General Program Chairman, Alan John Borner
    HazMat89 Central
  - University Curricula in the Marine Sciences and Related Fields, 1971-72 and 1972-73 (Box 5, Volume 10)
    Published by: The Oceanographer of the Navy
    Catalog
  - Guidance on Remedial Actions for Superfund Sites with PCB Contamination, August 1990 (Box 5, Volume 11)
    Government report, EPA/540/G-90/007
  - Field and Laboratory Microbial Ecology, 1972 (Box 5, Volume 12)
    Robert W. Gorden
    Field and Laboratory Manual
  - Marine and Estuarine Microbiology Laboratory Manual, 1975 (Box 5, Volume 13)
    R.R. Colwell, R.K. Sizemore, J.F. Carney, R.Y. Morita, J.D. Nelson Jr., J.H. Pickar, J.R. Schwarz, S.D. Van Valkenberg, J.D. Walker, R.T. Wright
  - Clinical Laboratory Electronics, 1972 (Box 5, Volume 14)
    David M. Jeffers, Frederick B. Lowe
    A Programmed Text
  - A Self-Contained Facility for Analyzing Near-Bottom Flow and Associated SEdiment Transport, October 1976 (Box 5, Volume 15)
    B. Lesht, R.V. White, R.L. Miller
    NOAA Technical Memorandum ERL MESA-9
  - Draft of a general scientific framework for a world ocean study, 1964 (Box 5, Volume 16)
    Intergovernmental Oceanographic Commission Unesco
    Draft of a study
  - Manual on international oceanographic data exchange, 1965 (Box 5, Volume 17)
    Intergovernmental Oceanographic Commission technical series 1
  - Data Administration for Marine Ecosystems Analysis, August 1978 (Box 5, Volume 18)
    Paul A. Eisen, Arleamon Sadler Jr., Marilyn. Scheffler
    NOAA Technical Memorandum ERL MESA-36
  - International Project on Paleolimnology and Late Cenozoic Climate No.2, 1979 (Box 5, Volume 19)
    Edited by: Shoji Horie
    IPPCCE Newsletter No. 2
  - Environmental Biology State-of-the-Art Seminar, April 1982 (Box 5, Volume 20)
    EPA, Editor: Patricia A. Archibald
    Seminar report, EPA-600/9-82-007
  - Symposium on the Recovery of Indicator Organisms Employing Membrane Filters, September 1977 (Box 5, Volume 21)
    EPA, Edited by: Robert H. Bordner, Clifford F. Frith, John A. Winter
    Symposium proceedings
  - Biological Analysis of Water and Wastewater, 1973 (Box 5, Volume 22)
    Application Manual
  - Workshop Microbial Degradation of Pollutants in Marine Environments, April 1979 (Box 5, Volume 23)
    Government report, EPA-600/9-79-012
  - RCRA Corrective Action Seminar, March 1990 (Box 5, Volume 24)
    Dames and Moore
    Seminar proceedings
  - Hazardous Workers Operations Refresher Training Course Manual, March 1989 (Box 5, Volume 25)
    Keystone Environmental Resources, Inc.
  - Pilot Scale Demonstration Study Engineered BioDegradation System(SM) Appendix to Feasibility Study nashua, New Hampshire, April 1989 (Box 5, Volume 26)
  - Northeast Monitoring Program 106-Mile Site Characterization Update, August 1983 (Box 5, Volume 27)
    Editors: John B. Pearce, Don C. Miller, Carl Berman
    NOAA Technical Memorandum NMFS-F/NEC-26
  - Bibliography of Articles from Commercial Online Databases Describing alternative and Innovative Technologies for Corrective Action and Site Remediation, December 1991 (Box 5, Volume 28)
    Hazardous Waste Superfund Collection EPA Headquarters Library
    Bibliography
  - Comparison of Four Plating Techniques and Four Media for the Enumeration of Heterotrophic Bacteria, October 1977 (Box 5, Volume 29)
    Ministry of the Environment, Ontario, The Honourable George A. Kerr, Q.C., Minister and K.H. Sharpe, Deputy Minister
    Comparative study
  - Instructions for Disk of the Month, 1990's (Box 6, Volume 1)
    Instruction manual
  - WordPerfect 5.1 Helpful Hints, Undated (Box 6, Volume 2)
    WordPerfect
  - Proceedings of the Symposium Microbiology of Power Plant Thermal Effluents, 1978 (Box 6, Volume 3)
    Editor: Robert M. Gerhold
    Proceedings of the symposium
  - New Product Development: From Research to Commercialization, August 1981 (Box 6, Volume 4)
    American Chemical Society, Carl Pacifico, Robert Polacek
  - General Test Methods, Nonmetal; Laboratory Apparatus; Statistical Methods; Space Simulation; Durability of Nonmetallic Materials, 1980 (Box 6, Volume 5)
    ASTM
    Annual Book of ASTM Standards
  - Marine Algal Assay Procedure: Bottle Test, December 1974 (Box 6, Volume 6)
    National Environmental Research Center
    Experiment manual and findings
  - Samplers Guide to the Contract Laboratory Program, December 1990 (Box 6, Volume 7)
    Guide, EPA/540/P-90/006
  - AATDF Technology Practices Manual for Surfactants and Cosolvents, February 1997 (Box 6, Volume 8)
    The AATDF Program Rice University, AATDF Report TR-97-2
  - Symposium on Gas, Oil and Environmental Biotechnology, 1993 (Box 6, Volume 9)
    Institute of Gas Technology
  - Annual Review of Biochemistry., 1974 (Box 6, Volume 10)
    Editors: Esmond E. Snell, Paul D. Boyer, Alton Meister, Charles C. Richardson
    Review Volume 43
  - Annual Review of Biochemistry., 1977 (Box 6, Volume 11)
    Review Volume 46
  - Bioremediation Continuing Education Course, February 20, 1989 (Box 6, Volume 12)
    Air and Waste Management Association
    Course No. 89C-1, Cincinnati, Ohio; course notes
  - The Proceedings of the Third National Outdoor Action on Aquifer Restoration, Ground Water Monitoring, and Geophysical Methods, May 1989 (Box 7, Volume 1)
    NWWA
    Proceedings of the conference, Includes an itinerary
  - Notes on the Rate of Growth of Tellina tenuis da Costa in the Firth of Clyde, May 1929 (Box 7, Volume 2)
    A.C. Stephen
    Reprinted from the Journal of the Marine Biological Association of the United Kingdom. Vol. XVI No. 1
  - The Muds of the Clyde Sea Area 1. Phosphate and Nitrogen Contents, March 1930 (Box 7, Volume 3)
    H.B. Moore
    Reprinted from the Journal of the Marine Biological Association of the United Kingdom. Vol. XVI No. 2
  - Bacteria of the Clyde Sea Area: A Quantitative Investigation, May 1930 (Box 7, Volume 4)
    Blodwen Llyod
    Reprinted from the Journal of the Marine Biological Association of the United Kingdom. Vol. XVI No. 3
  - The Muds of the Clyde Sea Area. III. Chemical and Physical Conditions; Rate and Nature of Sedimentation; and Fauna, June 1931 (Box 7, Volume 5)
    Hilary B. Moore
    Reprinted from the Journal of the Marine Biological Association of the United Kingdom. Vol. XVII No.2
  - Notes on the Biology of some Lamellibranchs in the Clyde Area, May 1932 (Box 7, Volume 6)
    Reprinted from the Journal of the Marine Biological Association of the United Kingdom. Vol. XVIII No. 1 Pages 51-68
  - A Survey of Clyde Plankton, 1924-1925 (Box 7, Volume 7)
    Sheina M. Marshall
    Reprint from the Proceedings of the Royal Society of Edinburgh Session 1924-1925 Vol. XLV-PartII-(No.12)
  - Oceanography and Marine Biology, 1966 (Box 7, Volume 8)
    Editor: Harold Barnes
    An Annual Review Volume 4
  - Chemical Oceanography., 1975 (Box 7, Volume 9)
    Editors: J.P. Riley and G. Skirrow
    2nd Edition Volume 2
  - Chemical Oceanography., 1975 (Box 7, Volume 10)
    2nd Edition Volume 3
  - Chemical Oceanography., 1978 (Box 7, Volume 11)
    2nd Edition Volume 7
  - FOCUS Conference on Eastern Regional Ground Water Issues, October 1992 (Box 7, Volume 12)
    National Ground Water Association
    Proceedings of the conference
  - International Conference on Water and Wastewater Microbiology, February 1988 (Box 7, Volume 13)
    Sponsors: International Association on Water Pollution Research and Control, ASM, NSF, UC Berkely, UC Irvine, UCLA, Orange County Water District
    Volume 1
  - International Conference on Water and Wastewater Microbiology, February 1988 (Box 7, Volume 14)
    Volume 2
  - Disposal in the Marine Environment An Oceanographic Assessment, 1976 (Box 7, Volume 15)
    National Academy of Sciences
    An Analytical Study for the U.S. EPA
  - Microbiological Fouling and its Control in Coastal Water and the Deep Ocean, September 1974 (Box 7, Volume 16)
    Stephen C. Dexter
    Technical Report prepared for the National Data Buoy Center
  - Ocean Disposal of Barge-Delivered Liquid and Solid Wastes from U.S. Coastal Cities, 1971 (Box 7, Volume 17)
    David D. Smith and Robert P. Brown
    Written for the Solid Waste Management Office EPA
  - Environmental Impacts of Dredging in Estuaries, 1977 (Box 7, Volume 19)
    Oregon State University, Corvallis
    Prepared for NSF, Applied Science and Research
  - Water Quality Data of the Delaware Estuary, Bay, and Selected Tributaries 1974, 1976 (Box 7, Volume 20)
    Delaware River Basin Commission
  - Assessment of the Factors Controlling the Long-Term Fate of Dredged Material Deposited in Unconfined Subaqueous Disposal Areas, December 1974 (Box 7, Volume 21)
    Texas A and M University
    Prepared for Army Engineer Waterways Experiment Station
  - Aquatic Disposal Field Investigations Duwamish Waterway Disposal Site Puget Sound, Washington, August 1978 (Box 7, Volume 22)
    C. Rex Bingham
  - Water Quality Impacts of Aquatic Dredged Material Disposal (Laboratory Investigations), August 1978 (Box 7, Volume 23)
    Sterling A. Burks and Robert M. Engler
  - Effects of Dredging and Disposal on Aquatic Organisms, August 1973 (Box 7, Volume 24)
    Nina D. Hirsch
  - Effects of Dredging and Disposal on Aquatic Organisms, August 1978 (Box 7, Volume 25)
    Nina D. Hirsch, Louis H. DiSalvo, Richard Peddicord
  - Design of a Laboratory Microcosm for Evaluating Effects of Dredged Material Disposal on Marsh-Estuarine Ecosystems, August 1978 (Box 7, Volume 26)
    Ecosystem Research and Simulation Division
  - FAO/UNEP Expert Consultation on Contaminant Monitoring - Data on Contaminants in Aquatic Organisms, November 1974 (Box 8, Volume 1)
    FAO and UNEP
    Report
  - Pollutants in the Aquatic Environment: Detection, Measurement, and Monitoring, 1976 (Box 8, Volume 2)
    FAO
    2 Copies; Lectures presented at the Second FAO/SIDA Training Course on Marine Pollution to Protection of Living Resources
  - Study of Microbial Activity and Crude Oil-Microbial Interactions in the Waters and Sediments of Cook Inlet and the Beaufort Sea, March 1978 (Box 8, Volume 3)
    Robert P. Griffiths and Richard Y. Mortis
    Third Annual Report
  - Marine Pollution Papers Oceans '82, 1982 (Box 8, Volume 4)
    Michael A. Champ
    Reprinted from Marine Pollution Sessions of Oceans '82 Conference Proceedings
  - Second Annotated Bibliography on Biological Effects of Metals on Aquatic Environments, October 1975 (Box 8, Volume 5)
    Environmental Research Laboratory
  - Ecological Monitoring of Aqueous Effluents from Petroleum Refineries, 1982 (Box 8, Volume 6)
    CONCAWE The Hague (Netherlands); F.G. Payne, C. Girton, W. de Ligny, A. De Roocker, A. Sirvins, W.J. Syratt, J.F. Tapp, R.H. Jenkins, H.J. Somerville
  - Effects of Ocean Disposal Activities of Mid-Continental Shelf Environment Off Delaware and Maryland, January 1975 (Box 8, Volume 7)
    Donald W. Lear
  - Summary of the Physical Oceanographic Processes and Features Pertinent to Pollution Distribution in the Coastal and Offshore Waters of the Northeastern United States, Virginia to Maine, December 1982 (Box 8, Volume 8)
    NOAA Technical Memorandum NMFS-F/NEC-17
  - First National Outdoor Action Conference on Aquifer Restoration, Ground Water Monitoring, and Geophysical Methods, May 1-21, 1987 (Box 8, Volume 9)
    The Association of Ground Water Scientists and Engineers (Division of NWWA) and U.S. EPA - EMSL - Las Vegas
    Proceedings of the Conference
  - Proceedings of the Petroleum Hydrocarbons and Organic Chemicals in Ground Water: Prevention, Detection, and Restoration A Conference and Exposition, November 20-22, 1991 (Box 8, Volume 10)
    The Association of Ground Water Scientists and Engineers (a division of NWWA) and The American Petroleum Institute
    Ground Water Management Book 8 of the Series
  - Proceedings of: Petroleum Hydrocarbons and Organic Chemicals in Ground Water: Prevention, Detection, and Restoration - A Conference and Exposition, November 17-19, 1987 (Box 8, Volume 11)
    NWWA and American Petroleum Institute
  - The Program of the Petroleum Hydrocarbons and Organic Chemicals in Ground Water: Prevention, Detection, and Restoration - A Conference and Exposition., November 15-17, 1989 (Box 8, Volume 12)
    The Association of Ground Water Scientists and Engineers, division of NWWA, and The American Petroleum Institute
    Program of the conference
  - The Proceedings of the Petroleum Hydrocarbons and Organic Chemicals in Ground Water: Prevention, Detection, and Restoration - A Conference and Exposition., November 15-17, 1989 (Box 8, Volume 13)
  - The Program of the Petroleum Hydrocarbons and Organic Chemicals in Ground Water: Prevention, Detection, and Restoration - A Conference and Exposition., November 9-11, 1988 (Box 8, Volume 14)
  - The Proceedings of the Petroleum Hydrocarbons and Organic Chemicals in Ground Water: Prevention, Detection, and Restoration - A Conference and Exposition., November 9-11, 1988 (Box 8, Volume 15)
    Proceedings of the conference - Volume 1
  - The Proceedings of the Petroleum Hydrocarbons and Organic Chemicals in Ground Water: Prevention, Detection, and Restoration - A Conference and Exposition., November 9-11, 1988 (Box 8, Volume 16)
    Proceedings of the conference - Volume 2
  - Petroleum Hydrocarbons and Organic Chemicals in Ground Water: Prevention, Detection, and Restoration - A Conference and Exposition., November 17-19, 1987 (Box 8, Volume 17)
    Proceedings of the conference, includes and itinerary for the conference
  - Sixth National Symposium and Exposition on Aquifer Restoration and Ground Water Monitoring, May 19-22, 1986 (Box 8, Volume 18)
    NWWA, Robert S. Kerr Environmental Research Laboratory, and EPA
  - Petroleum Hydrocarbons and Organic Chemicals in Ground Water: Prevention, Detection, and Restoration - A Conference and Exposition, November 12-14, 1986 (Box 8, Volume 19)
  - Abstracts accepted for presentation at FOCUS on Eastern Regional Ground Water Issues, Undated (Box 8, Volume 20)
    FOCUS
  - Proceedings of the 1992 Petroleum Hydrocarbons and Organic Chemicals in Ground Water: Prevention, Detection, and Restoration, November 4-6, 1992 (Box 8, Volume 21)
    The American Petroleum Institute and The Association of Ground Water Scientists and Engineers (a division of NGWA).
  - Petroleum Hydrocarbons and Organic Chemicals in Ground Water - Prevention, Detection, and Restoration - A Conference and Exposition, November 13-15, 1985 (Box 8, Volume 22)
  - Limnology in Developing Countries, 1995 (Box 9, Volume 1)
    Editors: Brij Gopal and Robert G. Wetzel
    Volume 1; International Association of Theoretical and Applied Limnology
  - Proceedings of the First Workshop on the Promotion of Limnology in the Developing Countries, August 29-30, 1980 (Box 9, Volume 2)
    Edited by: Syuiti Mori and Isao Ikusima
    Proceedings of the workshop
  - Mycology Lab Outline, Spring 1965 (Box 9, Volume 3)
    Class Notes
  - Field Notebook, Undated (Box 9, Volume 4)
    Field notes
  - Superfund '87, November 16-18, 1987 (Box 9, Volume 5)
    The Hazardous Materials Control Research Institute
    The Proceedings of the 8th National Conference
  - Superfund Innovative Technology Evaluation Program, November 1994 (Box 9, Volume 6)
    Technology Profiles Seventh Edition, EPA/540/R-94/526
  - Evaluation of Dredged Material Proposed for Ocean Disposal, February 1991 (Box 9, Volume 7)
    EPA and Department of the Army U.S. Army Corps of Engineers
    Testing manual
  - Water Quality Criteria 1972 (Box 10, Volume 1)
    Environmental Studies Board, National Academy of Sciences, National Academy of Engineering
    A Report of the Committee on Water Quality Criteria, At the request of and funded by the EPA
  - The Foliar Theory of the Flower, July-August 1975 (Box 10, Volume 2)
    Richard H. Eyde
    American Scientist, Volume 63 (tear out)
  - Bacterial Activity in Ground Waters Containing Petroleum Products, November 1973 (Box 10, Volume 3)
    J.H. Litchfield and L.C. Clark
    Final Report, Project OS 21.1, API Publication No. 4211
  - Research Vessel Eastward Fifteen Years of Service, 1978 (Box 10, Volume 4)
    John D. Costlow, Richard T. Barber
    Understanding Our Small, Wet Planet 1965-1978